FULL STACK DEVELOPER experienced in project management and marketing. Passionate about bringing ideas to life through code and learning new technologies. Admires great design / UX and will be a strong asset to a collaborative and creative team.

PROJECTS

- Food Truck Mapper --- foodtruckmapper.com
 - Javascript, NoSQL (MongoDB), Express, AngularJS, Node.js, Google Maps API, HTML/CSS, Material Design, Bootstrap, AWS
 - A full-stack web app using the Google Maps API for users to find food trucks nearby.
- Moto Listing --- motolisting.com
 PHP, MySQL, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, Codelgniter
 An interactive hub for motorcycle lovers to buy and sell bikes and hard to find parts.
- Check out my latest projects at: <u>kayrossio.com</u> & <u>github.com/krossio</u>

SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Responsive Web Design, jQuery, Javascript, AngularJS, Node.js, Bootstrap, Express, NoSQL (MongoDB), PHP, MySQL, CodeIgniter, Mongoose, AWS, RESTful Architecture, MVC's, TDD, OOP, Drupal, WordPress, Agile Methodologies, Git, Github, Bash, Google Analytics, AdWords, SEO, Balsamiq, Basecamp, Material Design

EXPERIENCE

- Digital Marketing Consulting 2014-2016 Increased and improved quality of leads for clients through website optimization, live chat, PPC and SEO. Managed pre-existing code and implemented new goal-driven features.
- Project Management, SEM & Analytics (Gravity Switch) 2011-2014
 Managed redesigns and new builds through every phase of the agile process. Lead PPC/SEO initiatives and specialized in Analytics. Optimized and created new processes for sales and marketing. Mentored junior managers and presented at local conferences.

EDUCATION

- Coding Dojo Full Stack Coding Bootcamp 2016
 Immersive web development bootcamp specialized in full stack training of the LAMP and MEAN stacks. Students become highly competitive with the latest technologies and equipped with the skills to efficiently learn new technologies for an ever-evolving industry.
- Salem State College B.A. Music 2006-2010